<ul>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=78255&amp;src=rss">West End Transitway Project</a></h2>
        <p>
            The City is proposing a Bus Rapid Transit (BRT) system along the Van Dorn/Beauregard corridor that will provide robust high-capacity transit operations between the Van Dorn Metrorail station, Shirlington Transit Center, Beauregard residential area and the Pentagon using a combination of dedicated and shared lanes. An overview of the proposed project and current study process was presented at the public kick-off meeting on May 22.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 18:26:34 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=77721&amp;src=rss">Absentee Voting for June 10 Democratic Primary</a></h2>
        <p>
            On Tuesday, June 10, there will be a Democratic Primary for U.S. House of Representatives (8th Congressional District). The deadline to apply for an absentee ballot by mail is Tuesday, June 3 at 5 p.m. The last day to cast an absentee ballot in-person is Saturday, June 7 at 5 p.m. The Voter Registration Office is open for in-person absentee voting Monday-Saturday from 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. with extended hours (until 7:30 p.m.) on June 2 and June 3.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 17:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=61880&amp;src=rss">DMV 2 Go Visits City Hall</a></h2>
        <p>
            The City and Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV) have once again partnered to bring “DMV 2 Go,” a mobile, full-service DMV customer service center to Alexandria. On Monday, June 9, the unit will park at City Hall from 9 a.m. to 4 p.m. Customers who have DMV transactions can skip the long lines and take care of them more quickly at the mobile unit.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 17:23:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=78211&amp;src=rss">Severe Thunderstorm Warning(3)</a></h2>
        <p>
            The National Weather Service has issued a Severe Thunderstorm Warning until 7:45 p.m. tonight.This storm is capable of producing damaging winds;  residents are advised to move indoors to a sturdy building and to avoid windows.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 23:40:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=16054&amp;src=rss">Special Features</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;Special issues and events in the City of Alexandria.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 12:40:06 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=16040&amp;src=rss">Shop, Dine, Stay, Celebrate!</a></h2>
        <p>
            Historic boutiques and art galleries; unique restaurants and outdoor dining; historic, state of the art, and pet-friendly hotels; events and activities for the whole family.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 13:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=16048&amp;src=rss">Historic Alexandria</a></h2>
        <p>
            Alexandria Visitor's Center, Alexandria's rich history, museums, and historic attractions.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 13:13:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=61340&amp;src=rss">Virginia's Hurricane Preparedness Sales Tax Holiday</a></h2>
        <p>
            Get ready for hurricane season--and save. Virginians who shop for products such as batteries, food storage containers, generators, first aid kits, bottled water, radios, and other preparedness products between May 25-31 can do both! During that time, shoppers won't pay sales tax on many useful items that cost up to $60, or on generators costing $1,000 or less.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 20:44:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=32818&amp;src=rss">Mayor Euille Today</a></h2>
        <p>
            On the latest episode of the &lt;em&gt;Mayor Euille Today&lt;/em&gt; show, Alexandria Mayor William D. Euille speaks with Yon Lambert and Brian Lawrence from Transportation &amp; Environmental Services (T&amp;ES) about spring and summer Maintenance projects and Resource Recovery programs; and with T&amp;ES Director Rich Baier, and ACVA President &amp; CEO Patricia Washington about the best ways to get to and around Alexandria.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 16:19:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=76712&amp;src=rss">City Council Adopts $636.8M Fiscal Year 2015 Budget</a></h2>
        <p>
            On May 1, the Alexandria City Council voted to adopt a $636.8M General Fund Operating Budget for FY 2015. The budget includes a half-cent increase in the real estate tax rate, and increased water and electric utility tax rates for commercial and industrial properties. It also includes an increased transfer to ACPS, continuation of the Elderly and Disabled Tax Relief and Senior Taxi programs, and expansion of rent relief for the elderly.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 23:54:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=72920&amp;src=rss">State of the City 2014</a></h2>
        <p>
            On April 22, Alexandria Mayor William D. Euille delivered his annual State of the City address which outlines the City's accomplishments, opportunities and challenges. The address was delivered at City Hall prior to the regular City Council legislative meeting.
        </p>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 15:56:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=19926&amp;src=rss">Register for Spring &amp; Summer Recreation Programs</a></h2>
        <p>
            Registration for Spring &amp; Summer 2014 classes and activities is now open! The Program Guide features a variety of summer camps and new programs such as fishing, babysitting training, self-defense, trips and more!
        </p>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 16:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=70334&amp;src=rss">Weather-Related Information, Cancellations &amp; Closings</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;The City clears snow from more than 560 lane miles of roadway, 20 miles of City-owned walkways and trails, and 44 acres of municipal parking lots or City-owned squares. Roads are plowed by priority , with primary and snow emergency routes cleared first, followed by secondary routes and then residential streets.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 16:14:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=19052&amp;src=rss">Utilities</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;The City of Alexandria does not operate any public utilities. The following companies providing service in Alexandria are regulated as utilities. Similar services may also be available from other providers.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=16060&amp;src=rss">News &amp; Media</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;News releases, webcasts, podcasts, RSS feeds, audio and video, FYI Alexandria, Channel 70, and more media from the City of Alexandria.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 16:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=55230&amp;src=rss">Celebrate the Holidays in Alexandria</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;Find seasonal information on holiday happenings in Alexandria, gifts and decorations, charitable giving opportunities, safety tips, and how to make your holiday "greener."&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 15:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=75427&amp;src=rss">Traffic Advisory</a></h2>
        <p>
            Residents are advised that during the evening of Sunday, Nov. 17, there will be increased traffic in area of W. Braddock Road near Kenwood Avenue, due to funeral services for Ronald Kirby, Transportation Planning Director for the Washington Metropolitan Council of Governments. &lt;br /&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 22:38:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=8498&amp;src=rss">How Do I?</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;Links for some popular topics&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 16:53:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=73559&amp;src=rss">Severe Thunderstorm Warning in Effect until 4:30 pm</a></h2>
        <p>
            The National Weather Service has issued a Severe Thunderstorm Warning for the City of Alexandria until 4:30 pm. Move indoors to a sturdy building; stay away from windows. &lt;br /&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 20:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=33154&amp;src=rss">Shop at the City's Farmers' Markets</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;Enjoy the season's fresh fruits, vegetables, baked goods, and more at Alexandria's farmers' markets! On weekends, the Market Square and Del Ray markets are year round on Saturdays; the West End Farmers' Market and the Four Mile Run Farmers' and Artisans Market are open on Sundays, May through November .&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 17:06:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=67210&amp;src=rss">Weddings &amp; Social Events</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p style="MARGIN: 0px;padding:0;"&gt;Make your wedding an historic occasion. Steeped in romance and authentic charm, Alexandria offers a variety of distinctive sites from colonial to contemporary, on land or sea, in beautiful buildings or the great outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=70902&amp;src=rss">Group Tours &amp; Motorcoach Information</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p style="MARGIN: 0px;padding:0;"&gt;Alexandria welcomes motorcoaches with free parking and all the resources necessary for a successful Alexandria visit.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=69794&amp;src=rss">One Eastbound Lane of Edsall Road Remains Closed</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;One eastbound lane of Edsall Rd. between S. Van Dorn and S. Reynolds Streets remains closed due to water main break-related repairs. Motorists are advised to use alternate routes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 22:49:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/index_quicklinks.aspx?id=69750&amp;src=rss">Edsall Rd. Closed Due to Water Main Break Repairs</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;Edsall Road between S. Van Dorn St. and S. Reynolds St. will remains closed for completion of repairs related to yesterday's water main break. Motorists are advised to avoid the area. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 16:21:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
    <li>
        <h2><a href="http://www.alexandriava.gov/goto.aspx?id=16026&amp;src=rss">Licenses &amp; Permits</a></h2>
        <p>
            &lt;p&gt;Construction permits and inspections, business licenses, code enforcement, zoning information, health permits.&lt;/p&gt;
        </p>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 18:49:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </li>
</ul>